<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

    <resources>
    <string name="app_name">Myapp</string>
    <string name="ada">Augusta Ada King, Countess of Lovelace (née Byron; 10 December 1815 – 27 November 1852) was an English mathematician and writer, chiefly known for her work on Charles Babbage proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine.
        She was the first to recognise that the machine had applications beyond pure calculation, and published the first algorithm intended to be carried out by such a machine.
        As a result, she is sometimes regarded as the first to recognise the full potential of a "computing machine" and one of the first computer programmers.</string>
        <string name="james">Gosling was with Sun Microsystems between 1984 and 2010 (26 years). He is known as the father of the Java programming language.He got the idea for the Java VM while writing a program to port software from a PERQ by translating Perq Q-Code to VAX assembler and emulating the hardware. He left Sun Microsystems on April 2, 2010 after it was acquired by the Oracle Corporation,citing reductions in pay, status, and decision-making ability, along with change of role and ethical challenges.He has since taken a very critical stance towards Oracle in interviews, noting that "during the integration meetings between Sun and Oracle, where we were being grilled about the patent situation between Sun and Google, we could see the Oracle lawyer's eyes sparkle."He clarified his position during the Oracle v Google trial over Android: "While I have differences with Oracle, in this case, they are on the right. Google totally slimed Sun. We were all really disturbed, even Jonathan Schwartz; he just decided to put on a happy face and tried to turn lemons into lemonade, which annoyed a lot of folks on Sun."However, he approved of the courts ruling that APIs should not be copyrightable.</string>
   <string name="c_ada">奥古斯塔·阿达·金，洛夫莱斯伯爵夫人(内拜伦;1815年12月10日- 1852年11月27日)，英国数学家、作家，主要以研究查尔斯·巴贝奇提出的机械通用计算机——分析引擎而闻名。
她是第一个认识到这台机器具有超越纯粹计算的应用的人，并发表了第一个打算由这台机器执行的算法。因此，她有时被认为是第一个认识到“计算机”的全部潜力的人，也是第一批计算机程序员之一。奥古斯塔·阿达·金，洛夫莱斯伯爵夫人(内拜伦;1815年12月10日- 1852年11月27日)，英国数学家、作家，主要以研究查尔斯·巴贝奇提出的机械通用计算机——分析引擎而闻名。
她是第一个认识到这台机器具有超越纯粹计算的应用的人，并发表了第一个打算由这台机器执行的算法。因此，她有时被认为是第一个认识到“计算机”的全部潜力的人，也是第一批计算机程序员之一。</string>
   <string name="c_james">高斯林在1984年到2010年间(26年)在太阳微系统公司工作。他被称为Java编程语言之父。他在编写从PERQ移植软件的程序时，通过将PERQ q代码转换为VAX汇编程序并模拟硬件，产生了Java VM的想法。2010年4月2日，在Sun微系统被甲骨文公司收购后，他离开了这家公司，理由是公司的薪酬、地位和决策能力都有所下降，同时角色也发生了变化，面临道德挑战。此后，他在采访中对甲骨文采取了非常关键的立场，指出“在Sun和甲骨文的整合会议上，我们被问及Sun和谷歌之间的专利情况，我们可以看到甲骨文律师的眼睛闪闪发光。”在甲骨文诉谷歌安卓案审判期间，他澄清了自己的立场:“虽然我和甲骨文有分歧，但在这件事上，他们是对的。谷歌完全粘住了太阳。我们都很不安，甚至乔纳森·施瓦茨;他只是决定装出一副高兴的样子，试着把柠檬变成柠檬汁，这惹恼了太阳上的很多人。不过，他同意法院的裁决，即api不应具有版权。</string>
    </resources>

